<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SpendRight</string>
    <string name="add_more"><u>ADD MORE</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Accounts</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Reports</string>
    <string name="THIS_MONTH">My Budgets</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms &amp; Conditions
    Updated at 2022-10-01
    General Terms
    By accessing and placing an order with SpendRight, you confirm that you are in agreement with and bound by the terms of service contained in the Terms &amp; Conditions outlined below. These terms apply to the entire website and any email or other type of communication between you and SpendRight.
    Under no circumstances shall SpendRight team be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, loss of data or profit, arising out of the use, or the inability to use, the materials on this site, even if SpendRight team or an authorized representative has been advised of the possibility of such damages. If your use of materials from this site results in the need for servicing, repair or correction of equipment or data, you assume any costs thereof.
    SpendRight will not be responsible for any outcome that may occur during the course of usage of our resources. We reserve the rights to change prices and revise the resources usage policy in any moment.

    License
    SpendRight grants you a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license to download, install and use the app strictly in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.
    These Terms &amp; Conditions are a contract between you and SpendRight (referred to in these Terms &amp; Conditions as "SpendRight", "us", "we" or "our"), the provider of the SpendRight website and the services accessible from the SpendRight website (which are collectively referred to in these Terms &amp; Conditions as the "SpendRight Service").
    You are agreeing to be bound by these Terms &amp; Conditions. If you do not agree to these Terms &amp; Conditions, please do not use the SpendRight Service. In these Terms &amp; Conditions, "you" refers both to you as an individual and to the entity you represent. If you violate any of these Terms &amp; Conditions, we reserve the right to cancel your account or block access to your account without notice.

    For this Terms &amp; Conditions:
    -Cookie: small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser. It is used to identify your browser, provide analytics, remember information about you such as your language preference or login information.
  -Company: when this policy mentions “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our,” it refers to Spendright Ltd, (2 Okwudili Ezenwankwo Drive, GRA Onitsha, Anambra State) that is responsible for your information under this Terms &amp; Conditions.
  -Country: where SpendRight or the owners/founders of SpendRight are based, in this case is Nigeria
  -Device: any internet connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer or any other device that can be used to visit SpendRight and use the services.
    -Service: refers to the service provided by SpendRight as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this platform.
  -Third-party service: refers to advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you.
  -Website: SpendRight."’s" site, which can be accessed via this URL:
  -You: a person or entity that is registered with SpendRight to use the Services.

    Your Suggestions
    Any feedback, comments, ideas, improvements or suggestions (collectively, "Suggestions") provided by you to SpendRight with respect to the app shall remain the sole and exclusive property of SpendRight.
    SpendRight shall be free to use, copy, modify, publish, or redistribute the Suggestions for any purpose and in any way without any credit or any compensation to you.

    Your Consent
    We have updated our Terms &amp; Conditions to provide you with complete transparency into what is being set when you visit our site and how its being used. By using our app, registering an account, or making a purchase, you hereby consent to our Terms &amp; Conditions.

    Modifications to Our app
    SpendRight reserves the right to modify, suspend or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the app or any service to which it connects, with or without notice and without liability to you

    Updates to Our app
    SpendRight may from time to time provide enhancements or improvements to the features/ functionality of the app, which may include patches, bug fixes, updates, upgrades and other modifications ("Updates").
    Updates may modify or delete certain features and/or functionalities of the app. You agree that SpendRight has no obligation to (i) provide any Updates, or (ii) continue to provide or enable any particular features and/or functionalities of the app to you.
    You further agree that all Updates will be (i) deemed to constitute an integral part of the app, and (ii) subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

    Indemnification
    You agree to indemnify and hold SpendRight and its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners and licensors (if any) harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys fees, due to or arising out of your: (a) use of the app; (b) violation of this Agreement or any law or regulation; or © violation of any right of a third party.

    Amendments to this Agreement
    SpendRight reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Agreement at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.
    By continuing to access or use our app after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, you are no longer authorized to use SpendRight.

    Updates to Our Terms
    We may change our Service and policies, and we may need to make changes to these Terms so that they accurately reflect our Service and policies. Unless otherwise required by law, we will notify you (for example, through our Service) before we make changes to these Terms and give you an opportunity to review them before they go into effect. Then, if you continue to use the Service, you will be bound by the updated Terms. If you do not want to agree to these or any updated Terms, you can delete your account.

    Intellectual Property
    The app and its entire contents, features and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, video and audio, and the design, selection and arrangement thereof), are owned by SpendRight, its licensors or other providers of such material and are protected by Nigeria and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws. The material may not be copied, modified, reproduced, downloaded or distributed in any way, in whole or in part, without the express prior written permission of SpendRight, unless and except as is expressly provided in these Terms &amp; Conditions. Any unauthorized use of the material is prohibited.

    Notice of Dispute
    In the event of a dispute, you or SpendRight must give the other a Notice of Dispute, which is a written statement that sets forth the name, address, and contact information of the party giving it, the facts giving rise to the dispute, and the relief requested. You must send any Notice of Dispute via email to: contact@spendright.ng. SpendRight will send any Notice of Dispute to you by mail to your address if we have it, or otherwise to your email address. You and SpendRight will attempt to resolve any dispute through informal negotiation within sixty (60) days from the date the Notice of Dispute is sent. After sixty (60) days, you or SpendRight may commence arbitration

    Disclaimer

    SpendRight is not responsible for any content, code or any other imprecision.

    SpendRight does not provide warranties or guarantees.

    In no event shall SpendRight be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or incidental damages or any damages whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort, arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service. SpendRight reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modifications to the contents on the Service at any time without prior notice.

    The SpendRight Service and its contents are provided "as is" and "as available" without any warranty or representations of any kind, whether express or implied. SpendRight is a distributor and not a publisher of the content supplied by third parties; as such, SpendRight exercises no editorial control over such content and makes no warranty or representation as to the accuracy, reliability or currency of any information, content, service or merchandise provided through or accessible via the SpendRight Service. Without limiting the foregoing, SpendRight specifically disclaims all warranties and representations in any content transmitted on or in connection with the SpendRight Service or on sites that may appear as links on the SpendRight Service, or in the products provided as a part of, or otherwise in connection with, the SpendRight Service, including without limitation any warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement of third party rights. No oral advice or written information given by SpendRight or any of its affiliates, employees, officers, directors, agents, or the like will create a warranty. Price and availability information is subject to change without notice. Without limiting the foregoing, SpendRight does not warrant that the SpendRight Service will be uninterrupted, uncorrupted, timely, or error-free.

    Contact Us
    Don not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions.

     -Via Email:  contact@spendright.ng
     -Via this Link:  https://spendright.ng/contact</string>
    <string name="assign_through"><u>ASSIGN THROUGH</u></string>
    <string name="set_budget"><u>SET BUDGET</u></string>
    <string name="my_budgets"><u>MY BUDGETS</u></string>
    <string name="checkInternet">Please Check Your Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1174011723346095</string>

    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1174011723346095</string>

    <string name="this_month">This month</string>
    <string name="view_all_plan"><u>View All Plan</u></string>
    <string name="date_wise_statement"><u>Statement</u></string>
    <string name="details"><u>Details</u></string>
    <string name="please_enter_com_otp">Please Enter Otp.</string>
    <string name="nire"> ₦</string>
    <string name="click_here"><u>Click Here</u></string>
    <string name="account_number">Account No</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend code</string>
    <string name="account_statement">Lets go! Please add a ledger account to start tracking your expense.</string>
    <string name="add_account">add account</string>
    <string name="enter_amount">Enter amount</string>
    <string name="please_enter_amount">Please enter amount</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="your_wallet_bal_is_low">Your wallet balance is low please fund your wallet.</string>
    <string name="select_an_option">Select an option to get started</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="email_or_username">Email or Username</string>
    <string name="use_finger_print">Use Fingerprint</string>
    <string name="facelock">Face Lock</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="confirmation_code">Confirmation Code</string>
    <string name="credit_wallet">Credit Wallet</string>
    <string name="set_budget1">Set Budget</string>
    <string name="fund_transfer">Fund Transfer</string>
    <string name="electricity">Electricity</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="airtime">Local and Foreign Airtime</string>
    <string name="cable">Cable TV</string>
    <string name="report">Transaction Report</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="legal_lastname">Legal Lastname</string>
    <string name="other_legalName">Other Legalname(s)</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="contact_information">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="referral_code">Referral Code</string>
    <string name="full_address">Full Address</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="verify_identity">Verify Identity</string>
    <string name="user_verification">User Verification</string>
    <string name="available_bal">Ledger Balance</string>
    <string name="refresh_balance">Refresh Balance</string>
    <string name="transfer_funds">Transfer Funds</string>
  <string name="wallet_to_wallet">Wallet to Wallet</string>
  <string name="wallet_to_bank">Wallet to Bank</string>
  <string name="wallet_to_virtual_card">Wallet to Virtual Card</string>
    <string name="transaction_ref">Transaction Ref</string>
  <string name="transaction_type">Transaction Type</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="pay_now">Pay Now</string>
    <string name="fund_my_virtual_card">Fund My Virtual Card</string>
    <string name="payment_complete">Payment Successful</string>
  <string name="back_to_home">Back to Home</string>
    <string name="enter_details">Enter Details</string>
  <string name="services_id">Services ID</string>
    <string name="phone_number1">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
  <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="my_virtual_card">My Virtual Cards</string>
    <string name="top_up">Top Up</string>
  <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="withdraw">Withdraw</string>
    <string name="unblock">Unblock</string>
  <string name="block">Block</string>
    <string name="transaction_summery">Transaction Summary</string>
  <string name="card_balance">Card Balance</string>
  <string name="create_virtual_card">Create Virtual Card</string>
  <string name="create_my_virtual_card">Create My Virtual Card</string>
  <string name="mr">Mr</string>
  <string name="mrs">Mrs</string>
  <string name="miss">Miss</string>
  <string name="card_name">Card Name</string>
  <string name="billing_address">Billing Address</string>
  <string name="card_pan">Card PAN</string>
  <string name="virtual_card">Virtual Card</string>
  <string name="all_virtual_card">All Virtual Cards</string>
  <string name="select_card">Select Card</string>
  <string name="naira_equivalent">Naira Equivalent</string>
  <string name="current_funding_rate">Current Funding Rate</string>
  <string name="beneficiary_account_number">Beneficiary Account Number</string>
  <string name="budget">Budget</string>
  <string name="settings">Setting</string>
  <string name="expense">Tracker</string>
  <string name="report1">Report</string>
    <string name="card_details">Card Details</string>
    <string name="current_withdraw_rate">Current Withdraw Rate</string>
    <string name="withdraw_from_virtual_card">Withdraw from Virtual Card</string>
    <string name="topup_virtual_card">Top Up Virtual Card</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="view_receipt">View Receipt</string>
    <string name="view_details">View Details</string>
  <string name="card_created_successfully">Card Created Successfully</string>
    <string name="fund_transfer_text_one">Multiple ways to withdraw funds</string>


  <string name="fund_transfer_text_three">Withdraw fund to your Wallet, to another SpendRight Wallet with their unique username or to your own bank account.</string>

  <string name="fund_transfer_text_two">Withdraw funds to another SpendRight user with their unique username and also withdraw to your own bank account instantly</string>
    <string name="virtual_card_text_one">Global Payments made easy</string>
    <string name="virtual_card_text_two">Make both local and cross border online payments with our trusted and secure virtual naira and dollar cards.</string>
    <string name="withdraw_from_my_virtual_card">Withdraw from My Virtual Card</string>
  <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="my_tracking_account">My Tracking Accounts</string>
    <string name="reserved_bank_account">Reserved Bank Account</string>
    <string name="atm_card_ussd">ATM card and USSD</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="tracking_accounts">Tracking Accounts</string>
  <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="terms_condition"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="biometrics_settings">Biometrics Settings</string>
    <string name="budget_categories">Budget Categories</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="budget_groups">Budget Groups</string>
    <string name="whatsApp">WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="rate_this_app">Rate this App</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="add_new_category">Add New Category</string>
    <string name="income">Income</string>
    <string name="add_budget_category">Add Budget Category</string>
  <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="category_name">Category Name</string>
    <string name="add_budget_group">Add Budget Group</string>
    <string name="group_name">Group Name</string>
  <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="profile_update">Profile Update</string>
    <string name="update_profile">Update Profile</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="tracking_account">Tracking Account</string>
    <string name="continue_to_budget">Continue to Budget</string>
  <string name="lock_your_money">Lock Your Money For Future Use</string>
    <string name="budget_tool_text">Our budgeting tools will prevent you from spending on stuffs you don’t really need, by locking away your funds based on set goals.</string>
    <string name="your_budget_define">Your Budget Defines Your Values</string>
  <string name="with_our_grouped">With our grouped budgeting approach, you can ensure that your spending reflects your core values by allocating the right amount of resources to defined groups.</string>
  <string name="repor">Report</string>
    <string name="budget_by_group">Budget by Groups</string>
    <string name="add_new_group">Add New Group</string>
    <string name="add_grp">Add Group</string>
    <string name="unbudgeted_money">"Unbudgeted Money : "</string>
    <string name="add_more_money">Add more money</string>
    <string name="withdraw_funds">Withdraw Fund</string>
    <string name="budget_amount">Budget Amount</string>
  <string name="due_date">Due Date</string>
    <string name="add_category">Add Category</string>
    <string name="please_enter_bvn_number">Please enter bvn number\n</string>
    <string name="please_enter_dob">Please enter dob\n</string>
  <string name="please_select_gender">Please select gender\n</string>
  <string name="accept_terms_condition">Accept terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="name_not_matched">Name not matched\n</string>
  <string name="dob_not_matched">Dob not matched</string>
  <string name="mobile_number_not_matched">Mobile number not matched</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose a color</string>
    <string name="group_created_successfully">Group created successfully</string>
    <string name="please_enter_grp_name">Please enter group name</string>
  <string name="please_enter_grp_des">Please enter group description</string>
  <string name="please_select_grp_color">Please select group color</string>
    <string name="no_grp_found">no group found please add.</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_delete_this_budget_group">Are you sure you want to delete this budget group?</string>
    <string name="no_category_found">"category not found "</string>
    <string name="please_enter_cat_name">Please enter category name</string>
    <string name="budget_category_created_successfully">Budget category created successfully.</string>
  <string name="expense_category_created_successfully">Expense category updated successfully.</string>
  <string name="income_category_created_successfully">Income category updated successfully.</string>

  <string name="please_select_category">Please select category</string>
  <string name="please_select_date">Please select date</string>
    <string name="choose_emoji">Choose Emoji</string>
    <string name="please_select_emoji">Please choose an appropriate Emoji</string>
    <string name="expense_categories">Expense Categories</string>
  <string name="income_categories">Income Categories</string>
    <string name="unblock_funds">Unlock Fund</string>
    <string name="refer_and_earn">Refer and Earn</string>
  <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="please_enter_referra_code">Please enter referral code</string>
    <string name="withdraw_to_wallet">Withdraw to My Wallet</string>
    <string name="withdraw_to_other_wallet">Withdraw to Other Wallet</string>
    <string name="withdraw_to_my_bank_account">Withdraw to My Bank Account</string>
    <string name="withdraw_to_another_wallet">Withdraw to Another Wallet</string>
    <string name="balance_to_withdraw">Balance To Withdraw : </string>
    <string name="choose_beneficiary">Choose Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="withdraw_to_your_bank">Withdraw To Your Bank</string>
    <string name="select_beneficiary">Select Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="enter_new_beneficiary">Enter New Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="add_beneficiary_to_list">Add Beneficiary to list</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
  <string name="edit_category">Edit Category</string>
    <string name="generate_account">Generate Account</string>
    <string name="perform_kyc">Perform KYC</string>
  <string name="click_copy">Copied</string>
    <string name="beneficiary_add_successfully">beneficiary added successfully</string>
  <string name="please_enter_account_number">Please enter account number</string>
    <string name="invalid_account_number">Invalid account number</string>
    <string name="add_new_beneficiary">Add New Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="add_beneficiary">Add Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="beneficiary_account_no">Beneficiary Account No</string>
    <string name="beneficiary_bank">Beneficiary Bank</string>
  <string name="confirm_your_payment">Confirm Your Payment</string>
  <string name="fees">Fee</string>
  <string name="amounts">Amount</string>
  <string name="expense_tracking_account">Expense Tracking Account</string>
    <string name="expense_category">Expense Category</string>
    <string name="amount_must_be_lessthen_from_available_amount">Amount must be less or equal to this budget amount</string>
    <string name="withdraw_complete">Withdrawal Successful</string>
    <string name="manage_beneficiary">Manage Beneficiary</string>
    <string name="not_found">not available</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_delete_this_beneficiary_account">Are you sure you want to delete this beneficiary account?</string>
  <string name="enter_username">Enter username</string>
    <string name="edit_expense_category">Edit Expense Category</string>
  <string name="delete_budget_category">Delete Budget Category?</string>
    <string name="withraw_bal_more_then_fees">Balance to withdraw is more than</string>
  <string name="withraw_bal_then_then">Balance to withdraw is less than or equal t main balance</string>

  <string name="you_can_onlY_withdraw_to_your_bank_account">You can only withdraw to your own bank account.</string>
    <string name="select_from_date">select from date</string>
  <string name="select_to_date">select to date</string>
  <string name="select_from_amt">select from amount</string>
  <string name="select_to_amt">select to amount</string>
  <string name="select_type">select type</string>
    <string name="txt_fund_available">On the selected due date, the fund will automatically be available on your wallet. You can also withdraw fund anytime to your wallet, bank account or virtual card in cases of emergency.</string>
  <string name="txt_fund_not_available">Instead of deleting this category, you can edit, to add fund and extend budget.</string>
  <string name="fund_available">Fund available on demand</string>
  <string name="fund_not_available">*Add Fund to this Category*</string>
    <string name="userid">User ID</string>
    <string name="balance">"Balance : "</string>
    <string name="beneficiary_username">Beneficiary Username</string>
  <string name="beneficiary_phone">Beneficiary Phone No</string>
    <string name="enter_legal_lastname">enter legal lastname</string>
    <string name="enter_legal_other">enter other legalname(s)</string>
  <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_delete_this_account">Are you sure you want to delete this account?</string>
  <string name="profile_updated_successfully">Profile updated successfully.</string>
  <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="password_change_successfully">password change successfully.</string>
    <string name="kyc_completed">KYC Completed</string>
  <string name="kyc_status">KYC Status</string>

  <string name="channelId">1</string>
  <string name="fund_ready_to_withdraw">Fund Ready for Withdrawal</string>
  <string name="text_fund_withdraw">Withdraw fund to meet deadline or edit to extend budget</string>


</resources>
